Guide to the Thomas B. Deen papers, 1957-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Meetings and Events, April 1962-October 1994
  - Subseries 1.1: Lectures and Speeches, October 1976-March 1994
    - Urban Mass Transportation Administration- Ralph Stanley Briefing, April 1981-November 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Assistant Secretary Judith Dot Briefing, July 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency Briefing, August-September 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - National Highway Traffic Safety Administration Briefing, February 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Rim, February-July 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Road Gang, February-March 1994 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - National Asphalt Pavement Association's 39th Annual Convention and Trade Show, 1994, September 1993-February 1994 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Coordinating Council, January-July 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Research, September 1961-June 1993
  Research materials and documents from location tours. Material in this series includes research reports, correspondence, project status reports, memos, notes, travel information, articles, essays, organizational charts, budget information, publication lists, maps, research reports, newsletters, pamphlets, biographical sketches, agendas and project proposals. Subject matter includes road maintenance, automobile assembly, transportation policy, urban mobility, automobile safety, the Transportation Research Board, the US Army Corps of Engineers, intelligent vehicles, and testing.
  - Pothole Report, February-March 1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Project Status Reports, February 1983, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Project Status Report, September 1982, January-December 1982 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Project Status Reviews, October 1981-January 1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Transportation Research Board Project Status Reports, April 1974-January 1982 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers Supreme Court Decision 1982, May-June 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - American Trucking Association Research Committee, Chicago, September-December 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - General Motors Plant Tour- Michigan Sites, January-April 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Safety Belt Use, June 1982, January 1980-September 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - North Dakota Department of Transportation Visit, November 1982-July 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Honolulu, Hawaii, June 1981-August 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - West Virginia State Visit, May-June 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Montana Department of Transportation Visit, June 1982-July 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Utah Department of Transportation Visit, Salt Lake City, April-July 1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Alabama, Arkansas, Louisiana- State Visits, June/July 1981, April 1980-May 1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - New York Department of Transportation-Albany, New York, January 1980-October 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Swedish Road and Traffic Research Institute, June-August 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - New Hampshire and Connecticut- State Visits April 1981, June 1980-April 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Kentucky, Tennessee, Florida- State Visits, December 1979-July 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Transbus 1979, March 1977-September 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility- Rice Center, December 1982-October 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research-Rice Center Advisory Board, February-July 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - MVP, Lather, Germany, June-October 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Research Center (Injury Prevention), July 1988-May 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Capacity Research, July-September 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Transportation Research Board, August-November 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Alliance for Transportation Research, July-August 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The American Association of State Highway Officials Road Test- Special Report 61A, September 1961 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Select Comittee on Research- JH451, February-September 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Drew Lewis Information- Department of Transportation 1980, November-December 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - World Link 1990, May 1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Research Award Program (Air) 1986-88, September-October 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - US Army Corps of Engineers, March-April 1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Los Alamos, New Mexico, August 1991-April 1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - External Advisory Board for the Massachusetts Institute of Technology Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Research Center of Excellence 1993, May-June 1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - OAMTC Academy, Vienna 1991, September 1989-October 1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Federal Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Recommendations 1 of 2, October 1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Federal Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Recommendations 2 of 2, October 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society in Japan, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Recommended Program of Research and Operational Testing, March 1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Activity, May-August 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society-Committee on Standards and Protocols, December 1992-January 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems, October 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems America, June-August 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Research and Development Program on Intelligent Vehicle-Highway Systems Using I-15 Facilities, July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems Vision, March-June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems 1990 Summary, July 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Research Service Report for Congress, February 1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Series 3: Correspondence, August 1979-September 1995
  Correspondence to and from Thomas Deen. Topics include travel, upcoming events, research, transportation, traffic laws, intelligent vehicles, transportation studies, Amnesty International, traffic management, transit research, highway administration and infrastructure.
  - National Committee on Uniform Traffic Laws and Ordinances 1981-82, September 1981-February 1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Canadian and Mexican Academies of Sciences, April 1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Timothy A. Patton, 1981-82, July 1981-May 1982 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Extern Program- University of Virginia, 1985, June 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Amnesty International- Syrian Engineers 1984, October 1983-May 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Institutue for Strategic Transportation Studies 1990, February-December 1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Institutue for Strategic Transportation Studies 1989, January-December 1989 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Institutue for Strategic Transportation Studies 1988, January-December 1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1993 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1992 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, July-October 1982 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Yacov Zahavi, March-November 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Marty Wohl 1979-83, August 1979-September 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Australia-Correspondence, August 1981-December 1982 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - London Correspondence 1981, February-May 1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Committees-Coordinating Council, March-June 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Committees-Advanced Traffic Management Systems, August 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Committees-Advanced Traveller Information Systems, May-August 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Committees-Commercial Vehicle Operations, March 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Committees-Advanced Vehicle Control Systems, August-September 1991 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Committees-American Public Transportation Systems, June 1991-July 1992 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Committees-Evaluations, Benefits, August 1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Committees-Safety and Human Factors, July 1991-October 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Committees-Standards, June 1991-May 1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Committees-System Architecture, May-August 1991 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Committees-Strategic Planning Subcommittee, March 1991-December 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Committees-Legal, October 1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Committees-Institutional, April-July 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Committees-Jefferson Group, August-October 1991 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Committees-Legislative Bills, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, January-October 1990 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Atlanta and Pacific Exchange Program, September-October 1990 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with Piminta, September 1990-October 1992 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Federal Highway Administration- Building Dedication- Fred Turner, February-April 1983 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Tom Hagedorn- Transit Research Council 1993, February 1993 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Mike Meyers, September 1990-December 1993 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Facilities 1989, February-March 1989 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Facilities 1988, January 1987-August 1988 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Deen- Correspondence 1982-84, March 1982-October 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Paid Invoices, August 1980-December 1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Paid Invoices, May-August 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence 1988-89, June 1987-March 1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1988, December 1986-December 1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1984-87, December 1984-July 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous 1993 1 of 2, July 1993-September 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous 1993 2 of 2, February 1992-September 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence on Meetings 1994, July-August 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- National Asphalt Pavement Association Meetings and Events 1994, January 1994-September 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Chinese- Koreans, etc., May 1989-August 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Consultations- I-95 Project, February-April 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Consumers Union, August 1990-January 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Book- Public Transportation, December 1989-February 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Julian Count von Heisermann 1993, March-August 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 1994, February 1992-July 1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 1993, May 1993-February 1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 1992, December 1991-December 1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 1991, December 1990-December 1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 1990, August 1988-December 1990 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 1994, August 1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Series 4: Planning, April 1981-August 1994
  Documents dealing with urban planning. Material includes booklets, receipts, newsletters, articles, correspondence, essays, notes, meeting agendas and schedules, memos, meeting minutes, presentation slides and Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Planning Committee documents. Subject matter includes transportation planning on a federal and local level, traffic congestion, transportation engineering, and intelligent vehicles.
  - National Capital Planning Commission, Washington, DC, August 1984-February 1986 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Urban Traffic Congestion Institute of Transportation Engineers Planning Committee, Williamsburg, Virginia, December 1984-March 1985 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Urban Transportation Planning, Airlie House, Virginia, November 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Planning Committee, June-August 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Transport Research and Computation (International) Co Ltd 1981-84, April 1981-June 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Federal Highway Administrators/Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society-Tactical Plan Committee, January-March 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Tactical Planning Committee-Planning Subcommittee, June 1991-May 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Tactical Plan Committee Minutes-Coordinating Council, January-February 1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Planning Subcommittees 199 1 of 2, June-November 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Planning Subcommittees 1993 2 of 2, January-June 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Plan Draft II 1 of 4, May 1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Plan Draft II 2 of 4, May 1994 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Plan Draft II 3 of 4, May 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program Plan Draft II 4 of 4, May 1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Miscellaneous 1 of 2, May 1993-August 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Miscellaneous 2 of 2, December 1993-May 1994 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - National Program Plan for Intelligent Vehicle Highway System (IVHS), October 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society-Annual Report 1993, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Membership Directory, May 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Architecture Development Program, April 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Plan for Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society in the United States 1 of 2, May 1992 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Plan for Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society in the United States 2 of 2, May 1992 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Outlining a National Intelligent Vehicle Highway Society Program, May 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Prospectus for a Cooperative Program Between Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Industry Partners, July 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Series 5: Publications, February 1957-October 1995
  Publications by Thomas Deen. Subject matter includes transportation, rapid transit, transportation engineering, highway research, traveler response evaluation, transit planning, the Alan M. Voorhees and Associates firm, urban public transportation, public works, transportation planning, rail transit, bridge inspection, automotive safety, the 55 mile per hour speed limit, fiscal policies, growth, asphalt, labor, transportation statistics, Caracas, Venezuela, parking prices, planning, foreign highway research programs, urban transportation planning, and economic evaluation.
  - Transport of Solid Commodities Via Freight Pipeline, July 1976-May 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Transit Journal, Volume 2, Number 4, November 1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Guidelines for Evaluating the Cost Effectiveness of Rapid Transit Projects, October 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Engineering Journal, August 1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Highway Research Record No.459, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Design of Procedures to Evaluate Traveler Responses to Changes in Transportation System Supply, September 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Transit Planning- Transportation Research Record 559, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - The Potential For Transit Standards, February 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Alan M. Voorhees and Associates Tech Notes-Volume 11, Number 8, Janunary 1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Research Needs for Evaluating Urban Public Transportation, July 1975 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Systems Analysis for Social Problems, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Analytical Gateways to Transport Expansion, May 1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Highway Research Record Number 293, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Highway Research Record Number 238, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Highway Research Record Number 205, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Highway Research Record Number 38, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Highway Research Record Number 130, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings of the Modal Choice and Transit Planning Committee, March 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Public Works-Volume 115, Number 1, January 1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - The Eleventh Australian Road Research Board Conference, August 1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Quarterly-Volume 37, Number 2, April 1983 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - News Report-Volume 33, Number 6, July-August 1983 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings of International Symposium on Surface Transportation System Performance Volume 1, October 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of International Symposium on Surface Transportation System Performance Volume 2, October 1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Public Works-Volume 114, Number 10, September-October 1983 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Transportation-Volume 12, Number 3, May 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Highway Research Record Number 318, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Transportation Quarterly-Volume 40, Number 1, January 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Highway Infrastructure Opportunities for Innovation, July 1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Emerging Transportation Planning Methods, August 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Engineering Journal of American Society of Civil Engineers, May 1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Urban Transportation Financing, July 1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Transportation System Management, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Traffic Quarterly-Volume 31, Number 1, January 1977 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Making Public Transit Happen, April 1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Transportation System Management in 1980 (Special) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Second Generation U.S. Rail Transit Systems: Prospects and Perils, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Urban Transportation Perspectives and Prospects, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rapid Transit Mode Selection, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Inspection and Rehabilitation, December 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Road Transportation Research, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the Automotive Safety Foundation- 1992 Safety Symposium, March 1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Surface Transportation and the Information Age, May-November 1992 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - The Northwest Technology Transfer Center Bulletin, July 1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Transportation and Mathematical Sciences, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Public Works, January 1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Transportation Engineers Journal-Volume 54, Number 8, August 1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - The Evolution of Transportation Planning, August 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Revitalization of Highway Research in America, Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Safety Benefits of the 55 Mph Speed Limits, July 1985 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Fiscal Policies and Transportation Planning, Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation of a New Modal Split Procedure, April 1964 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Effectiveness of Speed Limit Signs, April 1959 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Discussion Paper, January 1966 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Accelerated Testing of Pavements, August 1985 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Acceleration Lane Lengths for Heavy Commercial Vehicles, February 1957 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - The Use of Travel Time as a Factor in Rating Urban Streets, January 1960 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky Transportation Center, November 1988-October 1989 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - World Conference on Transportation Research 1986, May 1986 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Transportation Infrastructure, December 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - A Regional Conference on Growth and Transportation, November 1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Public Transportation, December 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of Mass Rapid Transit System Seminar, December 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bridge Inspection and Rehabilitation, December 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - World Link-Volume 3, Number 7,8, July-August 1990 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the 1st International Conference, January 1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Hot Mix Asphalt Technology, December 1990-January 1991 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Transportation Quarterly-Volume 41, Number 1, January 1987 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Seventy-Third Annual American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials Meeting Proceedings 1987, December 1987 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the 36th Annual Arizona Conferenc on Roads and Streets, April 1987 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 2nd North American Conference on Managing Pavements Proceedings, November 1987 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Highway Research Program, April 1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Practical Implications of Some Fundamental Properties of Travel Demand Models, January 1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Results From University College London, February 1971 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - The Impact of Rapid Transit Stations on Land Use Changes in Their Proximity Towards a Model 1 of 2, May-September 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - The Impact of Rapid Transit Stations on Land Use Changes in Their Proximity Towards a Model 2 of 2, May-September 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - The Dial-A-Ride, September 1970-March 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Transportation for the Disadvantaged, October 1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Labor in the Transportation Industries, February 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Summary of National Transportation Statistics, November 1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - The Role of Travel Time Limits in Urban Growth, April 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Special Area Analysis- Draft Manual, March 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - A Disaggregated Behavioral Model of Urban Travel Demand, March 1972 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Change of Mode Parking, January-April 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - A Travel Function and an Algorithm, Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - The National Bureau of Economic Research Prototype Urban Simulation Model, March 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - The National Bureau of Economic Research Urban Simulation Model as a Theory of Urban Spatial Structure, October 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Policy Statement on Transportation in the Boston Region, November 1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum- Caracas Betterment Tax, December 1971-May 1972 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Patrones Existentes de Viajes al Trabajo, Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - The American Economy Review, September 1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Road User Charges in Central America, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Issues of Equity, Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Parking Prices in the Central Business District, October 1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Bus Priorities at Traffic Control Signals, June 1972 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Transportation Infrastructure Research and Technology, June 1983 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Transportation Infrastructure Research and Technology, June 1983 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Numbered Documents- 1-83, August 1960-March 1973 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Numbered Documents- 84-140, October 1958-November 1978 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Numbered Documents- 141-214, October 1970-October 1973 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Numbered Documents- 215-293, January 1966-June 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Numbered Documents- 294-364, September 1969-June 1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Numbered Documents- 365-421, March 1972-February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Numbered Documents- 423-485, November 1972-February 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Critical Decisions in the Rapid Transit Planning Process, August-September 1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Discussion, January-October 1973 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Economic, Social, and Environmental Implications of Areawide Personal Rapid Transit, July 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Planning for the Metro, July 1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Intermodal Transfers in Urban Travel, October 1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Estimation of Sub-Modal Split Within the Transit Mode, January 1967 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Application of a Modal Split Model to Travel Estimates, January 1963 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - State of Alaska, June 1983-September 1985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Oral Presentation to Congress, June 1983 (Box 45, Folder 13)